During the summer
before my senior year, I got lucky.
My life became the California dream
I always wanted.
I got a job at a place right by the beach.
Sure, I was busing tables,
but tips were good and my friends
would meet me after work,
and we'd just hang out.
It was perfect.
But most importantly, I had Ali.
She moved here six months ago,
and the moment I saw her, I just knew.
It's like everything had been
in black and white.
Suddenly, there was color.
It's crazy how one person
can change your life.
Ali?
It's Tyler. I'm here to rob you.
Alison, you home?
- Hey!
- Oh, you scared me.
Sorry. Hi.
Ali got me, and I got her.
That's the thing about love.
Love changes you.
We should go.
Are we really doing this?
Oh, yeah, it's happening.
It makes you do the things
you never thought you would do.
Let's move gracefully into Warrior One.
- What's up, Gil?
- Let me guess, let me guess. Spin class?
- Yoga.
- It was super close though.
Wow, Ty, she really has you tamed.
Bro, you work in a juice truck.
Okay. What can I get you guys?
One big smoothie, two straws?
- Do you want...
- Two.
Two? Two berry smoothies.
- Two straws. Anything else?
- Lavender cookie.
- You got it.
- Love you, Gil. Thank you!
So much, Gil!
- Some nice moves out there.
- Thanks.
Seriously, fastest girl on the field.
I wish Mom could watch me play.
What about me, huh?
I'm just glad I get to see you play.
Me too.
When you kick the goal that wins
the World Cup, you can thank me
for teaching you everything you know.
Okay.
Here.
What's this?
- Half now, half after dinner.
- Cool.
Don't you eat the whole thing. I see you.
What are we having?
I'll make you eggs.
Come on, it's your favorite.
- You going out?
- Mm-hmm.
- With Gil?
- Yep.
Is your girlfriend going?
What do you know about it,
you little spy?
Does Mom know?
No. Shh.
Okay, keep it on the DL. Our secret.
All right, Mom's home.
I love you. Be good.
- You got the dishes?
- Yep.
- All right.
- Have fun tonight.
I will.
She's not making me wait.
Can you hear yourself through that?
We agreed, together.
Well, I can't wait anymore.
- Are you kidding me?
- Dude...
- All right.
Ali's gonna be here any second!
Fan that shit out.
It's unhealthy to hold it in.
Oh, my gosh.
Ugh.
This is not helping... Oh, shit.
Baby!
Don't fuck this up.
Move, Gil!
- 'Sup, baby?
- Hi! Hi, boo.
- You look pretty.
- Thank you.
What's going on? What did I miss?
Is that a new perfume?
Well, you delinquents are late.
Sorry, Gil couldn't decide what to wear.
I could decide,
and I picked his mom's underwear.
They've been like this
since elementary school, FYI.
I figured.
Hey.
- Melinda!
- Hi!
- Happy Labor Day.
Thanks for having us over.
Aw. Enjoy your freedom while you can.
You look gorgeous, as always.
You guys need to stop bringing him.
Okay, I have something to show you guys.
I may just push you in the pool.
Uh-oh.
It's all the same people.
She wants you so bad.
It's kind of sad, to be honest.
Cheers, dude.
To a night full of endless possibilities.
Alison effin' Hewett!
- Oh, my God! I knew it was you!
- What are you doing here?
Wow, it's been a long time.
Wow, you look so sober.
- Like, why are you so sober?
- Tyler, this is Chase.
- What's going on, buddy?
- He's my friend from San Francisco.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hey, have a good time tonight, okay?
- I'll see...
- See you later. Wanna go?
Is he a friend of yours?
Just someone from San Francisco.
Ignore him.
Can you grab me a Diet Coke?
Yeah.
Going light tonight, bro?
It's for Alison.
Shit. Times change, huh?
You didn't know Alison back
in San Francisco, did you?
Whew.
It wasn't a party unless Ali was there.
You know, Ali Hewett.
She sucked it like a champ.
That was her thing.
She was en fuego, man.
I mean, she was,
oh God, just so hot.
But you know what I'm talking about.
You've tapped that, right?
Thanks. It was great meeting you.
I don't know
why she didn't introduce us sooner.
Great meeting you, too.
Motherfucker.
Hey, are you in line?
Uh...
Yeah, seems that way, doesn't it?
Now it does, yeah.
How's it going?
I got ditched tonight, so...
- Really?
- Mm.
Well, I just got humiliated upstairs,
so welcome to the club.
- I'm Holly.
- Tyler.
- Nice to meet you.
Sorry, who would ditch you? I don't...
I can't make the connection right now.
Who would humiliate you?
I wish it was that simple.
Isn't it?
Bye, Tyler.
- Yeah, it was pretty good.
- Do you know where Tyler went?
No.
There you are.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
- Hey, you all right? What's going on?
- Chase seems like a keeper.
What did he say to you?
He spoke very highly of you.
You slept with that guy, Ali?
You won't sleep with me,
but you did it with that guy?
- Hey, come on.
- Chase!
Yo, Chase!
Anything else you can tell me
about my girlfriend?
- We're all about sharing, right?
- Tyler.
- Stop it.
- Right?
- Dude, you need to chill out.
- I need to chill out?
- Tyler!
- Wipe that smile off your face...
Come on! We're going outside.
You're acting crazy. You need to go home.
- Okay. What, you want me to leave?
- Yeah.
So you can go hang out with Chase?
Are you serious?
Has this just been about sex
for you this whole time?
Because that's really disappointing.
Oh, so now I'm disappointing?
Sorry, how's that fair
when you're the one keeping the secrets?
We're done here. It's over.
Sick, right? It's not mine.
You look like you're having a great night.
I think I just got dumped.
Come on. Let's get out of here.
Come on!
You'll thank me later.
You're only gonna make it worse.
Where are we going?
I don't know.
You swallow, I swallow.
You found me.
Hey.
Come sit.
Where are we?
I know, right? It's crazy.
This place is so huge.
I've been house-sitting all summer,
but yet I still can't find my way around.
I can't believe anybody
actually lives here.
Me either.
Did you take all these?
Yeah.
Holly, you're really talented.
Thanks.
I, uh...
I sort of taught myself.
So...
Last night happened.
Yeah, I guess it did.
- Come on, I wanna show you something.
- Lead the way.
I'm pretty sure that's a fireable offense.
I'm not really a house-sitter at all.
I just broke in.
Holly?
♪ Time flies ♪
Hey!
♪ Door's open ♪
♪ Away goes the past ♪
♪ It's okay ♪
♪ Brave faces ♪
♪ Staring at me ♪
This pool is ridiculous.
It's like the size of my house.
Imagine having this kind of money.
I can't. I'm down with this pool, though.
I'll take it.
Yeah, my dad would have loved
something like this.
All he ever got to do was work
before he died.
He never got to enjoy anything.
I'm sorry.
♪ Are you ready? ♪
Do you have brothers and sisters?
No. I have a stepmom. She's fun.
We're not close.
But I'm only stuck with her
for another year, so...
- Where is she right now?
- I don't know.
London? Paris?
I couldn't even tell you.
She doesn't even bother
telling me anymore.
My mom's barely around too,
because she works so much.
My dad's nonexistent.
It's mostly just me and my little sister.
You know, she's...
She's young,
and I'm basically all she's got.
No way!
- Your laugh, I love it.
- I know, it's awful!
No, it's so good. It's so good.
- My girlfriend never even met my family.
- What?
- Yeah, I know.
- Why?
I don't know, she wouldn't get it.
She just lives in a different world.
I really like who I am when I'm with you.
Sometimes I think
maybe I'm just being my true self.
I like that.
Maybe I should just move to LA, huh?
Maybe I should just move to LA
and make you forget all about her.
Maybe you should.
Yeah.
♪ Get away ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ You wanna get away ♪
♪ There is no turning back
Get away ♪
You wanna get away ♪
♪ There is no turning back
Get away ♪
You're not staying over?
Hey, I should probably head out.
You know, I've been gone all day,
and my parents are probably worried.
I don't really know what's going on
with me right now,
but this...
this was really...
Special?
Yeah.
Yeah, it was special.
Thanks for everything, Holly.
Hey.
Look, let me just start by saying...
I get why you acted the way
you did at the party.
I'm sorry, but for what it's worth,
that guy Chase...
- The way he talked about you...
- Yeah, but that's his problem.
Okay?
Listen, Tyler...
If you need me to be some saintly virgin,
I'm not.
I was a totally different person
in San Francisco.
Okay, I hung out with a bunch of assholes.
Mainly.
I drank a lot. Got messed up.
Slept around.
We moved here
because my parents wanted me to get sober
and be a normal teenager
and honestly, so did I.
And that's what I've been doing.
Why didn't you just tell me
all this stuff?
I don't know, I guess I was just afraid
you'd be weirded out
or people would label me a slut,
or I don't know.
Ali, I'm not a guy
that cares what people think.
Okay, that's totally a lie.
All right, I care what you think.
Well, I think we were good together.
So does that mean
you wanna get back together?
Yes.
Now before we make any more
assumptions about each other,
I want you to know the real reason
why I wanted us to wait.
Ali...
- You don't have to explain yourself...
- No, let me finish.
Sex never meant anything to me.
Okay? And things are so different
with you, and...
I don't know, I guess I've never been
with somebody that I loved before.
I love you too, Ali.
No more secrets.
♪ Naked in the back seat ♪
Oh, good.
- Lyds!
- Hey!
- Hey, baby.
- The video's still going around.
- It's a dude falling down in yoga class.
- It was funny, come on!
- Yo, what up, Gil?
- Gil!
- What up, yo?
- What's up?
- Happy first day.
What's up?
Now it's kind of like
I have a famous boyfriend.
Does famous boyfriend get a kiss?
Like, one kiss? Can I get one kiss?
- I think just one.
- Just one?
- One.
- All right? Make it good.
What?
- What, baby?
- We should get to class.
- Let's go.
- All right.
Come on!
Welcome, welcome back, everybody.
New year, new class, new vistas.
Everybody ready to dive in?
Awesome! Let's do it.
And new student as well,
also joining us. Great.
We're gonna be learning about the cells
in your saliva.
So everybody pair up.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Let's dive in.
- Wanna be partners?
- What are you doing here?
Turns out the vacation
is not a vacation after all.
- My stepmom made it permanent.
- Oh, cool.
Yeah, so I thought I'd surprise you.
Surprise.
It's working.
So I saw you got back
with your girlfriend. That's good.
Yeah.
Did you tell her about us?
No, and I'd appreciate it
if we didn't make it a...
- Microscope.
- A thing.
- A thing? Oh, no.
- Slide a Q-tip...
I can be very discreet.
Cool.
- Hey, handsome!
- Hey! Hey.
- What's up?
- Just hanging out. What's going on?
Nothing. How are you?
G'day, mates. This is Holly.
We met earlier in biology class,
and she's the new girl.
Sorry, Alison, but get used to it.
Hi. I'm Alison.
Lydia and my boyfriend Tyler.
Oh, Tyler and I actually go way back...
to first period.
I saw you taking photos
with that camera. Sweet camera.
Oh, thanks. It's my pride and joy.
Some think that all photos
should be taken with an iPhone,
but others disagree
because we value quality.
Yeah, that's exactly why I take Polaroids.
Oh, that's awesome. I totally get that.
Do you wanna hang out this weekend?
Here, give me your number.
Yeah, actually I have tickets
to the Roxy tonight,
- if you guys are down.
- Oh, we're in, let's go, yeah.
- Yeah, why not? That sounds great.
- Yeah, for sure.
Tyler?
You know what?
I'm pretty beat, but you guys have fun.
Oh, my gosh.
- Really?
- You guys can have fun. Go have fun.
- What?
Yeah, I promised my little sister
I'd hang out with her tonight, so...
Suit yourself.
Hey, Ali,
did you wanna see the new photos?
Holly?
Holly, you down here?
- Hey.
Wow, you look sexy.
Holly, look. We need to talk, okay?
I brought you down here to talk.
Yeah, right.
Hey, Holly, I'm serious. Okay, listen.
We gotta stop this, all right?
What happened over summer, it was great,
but you know, we can't do this.
It was a mistake.
You said it was special.
I thought I was broken up with Ali.
I would've never have done that to her,
you know, if we were together.
- I just...
- You don't want me.
You gotta understand.
You lied to me.
You used me.
Holly.
- That it? You're an...
- No, no, no.
- Holly.
- Asshole.
- Holly, please.
- You think it's that easy?
- No.
- You're gonna be fucking sorry.
Thank you so much for those tickets.
That was cool.
Seriously, I'm so glad we saw them play.
Oh, we were just talking about it.
- Before they hit.
- In a small venue.
We can be like,
"We liked them before they were cool."
I was trying to add you the other day,
but I couldn't find your profile.
Is it like hidden or something?
Um...
Yeah, I erased it a year ago.
Kind of a cleanse, you know?
Well, that's weird.
Um...
The friends I still care about,
well, they know how to reach me.
Couldn't agree more.
Holly, these are great.
- Babe, you gotta see these. Look.
- What?
They're really good.
- Good, right?
- Yeah, that's really good.
Who's the guy?
That's a really long story.
Well, the lighting's very good.
Idea is detail shots and stuff
I think would look cool this way.
I love Tumblr. I get a lot
of my inspiration from there, yeah.
Let's go find Gil. Come on.
So the beach it is.
Okay.
- You have sand all over you.
- I know. It's this guy's fault.
You guys are so cute together.
You know, we have this thing.
I'll be thinking about Tyler, and then
I'll look at my phone a minute later,
and he texts me.
That is so dope.
Yeah, I know what that's like.
Oh, the guy from the picture earlier?
Come on, you gotta tell us.
Tell us! Tell us!
Well, actually we met right around here.
And... you know, when I first saw him,
I just knew instantly
that we had this connection.
Then I just died right there.
And then later, we wound up together
at this club, dancing and grinding,
and then I leaned in,
in the rush of the music and...
- What is she doing?
- I don't know.
- I'm gonna go.
- No!
- We have to hear the rest of the story.
- It's okay. He was a real asshole anyway.
- Holly, you ready?
- Hmm?
Yeah. Uh-huh.
- Thanks for driving, babe.
- Yeah.
- You sure you don't wanna stay?
- No. It's okay. We have got plans.
We have girl talk.
- What? Right now, girl talk?
- Yeah.
Thanks for driving. See you later.
- See you.
- Okay.
- Drive safely. Bye.
- Bye, baby.
Bye-bye.
- Text me.
- Okay.
Girl talk.
- Let's go!
- I'm coming.
I like her.
- This is really cute.
- That's like wearing a blanket.
Yeah, it's so soft.
You can borrow it sometime if you want.
Thanks.
I will then.
This is cute. Where's this from?
Oh. My mom got that for me
for my 16th birthday.
Yeah.
That's a really cute photo.
That was our second date.
We went to the farmer's market,
and they had all those food trucks
lined up,
and we got a sample from each one.
God, Tyler just seems like a great guy.
Yeah, I mean,
he has his moments like any of us,
but generally he's pretty great.
But how is he in bed?
We haven't actually
gotten there yet, so...
Oh...
I'm sorry, I...
No, it's not a big deal. No.
We're just, you know, taking it slow.
That's cool. I really respect that.
Thank you.
You know how guys are anyway
once you've had sex.
Bit my lip.
All right, man.
Thanks for the ride.
Yo, Gil, wait. Can we talk?
Like, seriously talk for a second?
Lay it on me.
I slept with Holly.
Do you remember the night
where I dipped out after Melinda's party?
- Yeah.
- I didn't go home that night.
Basically Ali broke up with me
and I went outside,
and I ran into Holly,
and things got out of hand, and...
Dude.
I didn't think it was serious, but just...
It was stupid.
- Well, how was it?
- Oh, no, man. I...
I think Holly's trying to mess with me.
Why would she be hanging out with Alison?
She's gonna tell her about it, I know it.
Yeah, 'cause she's kissing me
to mess with you.
She's hanging out with Alison and Lydia
and taking us all to the Roxy
to mess with you.
That's not what's happening right now.
You gotta listen to me, man.
I don't know.
I don't know what it is,
but something's wrong.
Everyone's weird, man.
That's your guilt talking.
I'm gonna tell Ali about it.
You just fixed things with Ali.
You can't tell Ali.
Why would you give that up?
Yeah, I'm probably gonna head out, man.
- Thanks for the ride, bro. I gotta go.
- Yeah.
- Your door sucks. See you tomorrow.
- See you.
- Tyler won't stop texting me.
- I think it's sweet.
- He's just trying to be a good boyfriend.
- Mm-hmm.
It's a little late, isn't it?
- Hi. Mom, this is Holly.
- Hi, Mrs. Hewett.
Thanks so much for having me over.
I really appreciate it.
Hi.
What's up?
Just making sure you don't need anything.
We're good.
- So you're okay?
- Yeah.
She seems upset.
No. She just worries.
I used to be kind of a mess.
- Yeah, I get that.
- Thanks.
What the hell are you doing here?
How do you know where I live?
Don't you wanna invite me inside?
I'd love to say hi to your sister.
Did you steal Ali's sweater?
No, she said she had no problem with me,
you know, sharing things of hers.
She knows.
What?
I told her everything.
It's okay though, Ty.
- She really likes us together.
- Why would you do that?
- Holly, why would you tell her?
- Come on.
Cuteness, I was kidding.
What, so you're lying?
Holly, did you tell her or not?
Come on, Ty,
do you really think I would do that?
- It's our little secret.
- You're insane.
Ouch.
What else have you lied about?
You're the only one who gets to lie?
This is crazy.
This isn't crazy.
Give it time.
Thank you for coming in, Mrs. Viola.
And I wouldn't worry just yet, okay?
We'll be keeping an eye
on her behavior here at school.
You keep an eye on her at home.
Okay?
Okay, thank you so much.
Hey, Miss Viola.
Sorry. I'm Tyler.
I'm a friend of your stepdaughter's.
Oh, is that right?
Yeah, I didn't wanna interrupt you.
Thought I'd introduce myself
and welcome you to the neighborhood.
- Oh, that's very sweet of you.
- How's she doing, by the way?
The last couple days
she's seemed kind of down.
I know it's hard, moving to a new
neighborhood, new place, new school.
It's not exactly Oakland, is it?
Oakland? We're from San Diego.
Oh, yeah, that's right. Sorry.
But I have been traveling a lot for work
lately, so she's been on her own.
We lost her father recently.
I don't know if she told you that.
It hasn't been easy.
Yeah, I was sorry to hear it.
But she's a good girl.
I believe that. She just gets...
- What's the word?
- Obsessed?
Lonely.
I gotta go.
Do me a favor.
Don't tell her that we spoke.
She wouldn't like that.
She's cool.
We stayed up all night talking,
and she's actually kind of nice.
It was a little weird, though.
I woke up Sunday, and she was just gone.
Like, no goodbye or anything.
That's what I'm saying.
I have this feeling about her.
- You're sounding like my mom.
- I'm serious.
I looked her up online. Nada.
She's a ghost person.
- You're stalking her?
- It's not stalking.
- Everybody Google searches.
- Okay, listen.
I know she's a little off,
but it's hard to be new here, okay?
- Just give her a chance.
- I don't buy it.
There's something else going on,
and I'm gonna find out what it is.
Be nice.
- Hey, I got your usuals.
- Thank you.
And here.
Thanks.
What happened to you this weekend?
You know, I woke up
with a stomach flu on Sunday.
Nothing worse than being sick
at someone else's house...
There's nothing worse
than a stomach bug. I swear, it's...
Yeah, it's the worst.
Are you feeling better?
I've been feeling weird
the past few days.
You know what really helps me with that
when I feel nauseous is ginger tea.
With a little lemon.
It just tastes good.
Oh, my God. Holy shit, is she choking?
She's having an allergy attack.
Someone get help.
I have to find her EpiPen.
Someone call for help!
- I'm gonna go.
- Okay.
God.
Hey, we need to talk.
Oh, my God,
I'm so happy to see you. I...
I didn't get any sleep last night.
Lydia... her doctor said
there was something in that smoothie.
She started coughing up blood
again last night.
- What?
- Yeah, it was...
It was horrible.
There was so much blood and...
- Oh, my God. Hey, baby, come here.
- I don't know.
I'm so lucky I have you.
Corinne, what an unpleasant surprise.
I thought you were in New York.
Try to remember,
I'm on your side here.
It's a little hard to remember that
when Dad left you everything.
You know what's mine is yours, right?
Right.
Providing you put in a little effort.
I know you've been missing
your therapy appointments.
I missed one.
Two. Dr. Gregory called me yesterday.
You were supposed to see him.
And your guidance counselor
is concerned, too.
Are you at least taking your medication?
I told you, I don't like the medication
they put me on.
It numbs me emotionally.
Sometimes that's a good thing.
I'm a very loving person, Corinne.
- I never said...
- And if I...
can't feel love...
well, you see, I'd rather just...
die.
You always forget
the silverware.
Can you please pass me the syrup?
You're so special, Tyler.
I don't understand.
Everything was going fine with Holly.
We were hitting it off.
I haven't talked to her in days.
- You think she's avoiding me?
- She's got a past we don't know about.
I don't know,
don't put yourself too far into it.
- Okay. She could have broken her phone.
- Whatever. Who cares?
You know, I'm sure she's fine.
I'm sure she's fine.
Oh, dude, there she is.
Dang, she looks upset.
What's going on?
Holly's pregnant.
Wha...
Yeah, it's crazy,
but she says she took, like, four tests.
So I don't know,
I guess the guy is a total asshole,
and he actually hit her...
he actually hit her.
I told Holly I'd hang out with her.
She just kind of needs someone right now.
Is that the guy?
I wish. He hasn't been in touch.
Are you serious?
He really needs to be there for you.
I know.
What would you do if it was Tyler's baby?
I mean, like, what would you do if
it was you and it was Tyler's baby?
Would you keep it?
I don't know. Um...
That's a big question.
Yeah, but you guys
are so perfect together.
You're gonna be one of those
high school couples
that gets married after college,
and they have kids, and it's so cute.
I'm sure his parents must love
the thought of you as a daughter-in-law.
Actually, I haven't met them yet.
Really?
- Why not?
- They work all the time.
It's really just him and his sister.
He's very private, so I try not to push.
That's so odd.
- You know that's, like, a little weird.
- I know, but it's fine. It's fine.
Your call.
Off the glass for two!
Inbound pass to the point guard,
who is surrounded by backcourt pressure.
He comes around two guards
before passing it...
Fakes left and goes right
along the baseline...
Annabelle.
Annabelle is my best friend...
- So, what grade are you in?
- I'm in third.
Third grade?
That must be a nice place to be.
Mm-hmm.
- Wait till you get...
- Tyler!
Hey, Ty.
- I love your nail polish.
- Thank you.
It's midnight fuchsia.
I'll get you a bottle sometime.
Midnight fuchsia. You're so pretty.
Oh, thank you. I'll tell you a secret.
I always wanted a little sister.
So maybe...
you and I can just hang out, us girls.
Hey, why don't I walk you out?
- No, not yet.
- Yeah, not yet.
Sorry, Tiff, she's got to go.
- Okay.
- It's okay. I'll be back soon.
Give me a hug.
You know, your sister seems real sweet.
I don't know why you never
introduced your girlfriend to her.
You're not my girlfriend.
No, you're right.
I'm not your girlfriend at all.
I'm some whore you knocked up
and then left and tried to ignore.
Honestly, Holly, what do you want from me?
Okay, I'm 17. Look at where I live!
Think I can support you and a kid?
I'm trying to be good,
but we gotta come up with some plan
because this isn't working.
You don't need to support me, baby.
What don't you understand?
As long as we're together, it's perfect.
I know how much you love me,
and I know you just can't see it
because of that bitch!
No, Holly.
You were a mistake.
I know you love...
Just stay away from me.
I mean it, Holly.
Can I just, um...
Holly?
We're still in contact,
and I went over to his house...
- I really didn't know who to call.
- No, it's okay. Just sit.
- What's going on? Holly?
- We have a lot to talk about.
I haven't been completely honest
with you.
Okay.
That guy, we have been in contact,
and I went over to his house,
and we had a fight,
and he pushed me to the ground.
Oh, my God, Holly.
God. And I just...
- We need to tell someone.
- No, no. It's more complicated.
You know what, I just...
I really just need to calm down
for a moment.
Okay. That's fine. It's okay.
Just this guy from the summer, I...
I really just need to tell you the truth.
Hey.
I got you some flowers.
I hope you're not allergic to those.
Mm, no. Thank God.
How's the hospital? Hot nurses?
Oh.
- The sponge baths are great.
- Ooh.
Oh, yeah.
What's up with you?
Did Holly know about your allergy?
Yeah.
Maybe. I don't know.
Does any part of you think
that this wasn't an accident?
Ali and I get the same smoothies
every single day.
The one time Holly gets them for us,
I have an allergy attack?
I gotta tell you something about Holly.
Me and Holly, we...
Jesus, Ty.
This all makes a little bit
more sense now.
- You've got to tell...
- I'm gonna tell Ali. I'm gonna tell her.
All right, this is my mess.
I'm gonna fix this.
Be careful.
Hi, you've reached Ali.
Leave a message and I'll get back to you.
Ali, I got to tell you something.
I slept with Holly.
I know.
She showed me pictures.
Yeah. Pictures of you sleeping.
Pictures of you guys up
in some big house together.
Pictures of her with your family.
You let me be friends with her
this whole time.
Do you even know how that makes me feel?
No, Ali, that's not how it was, okay?
We were broken up.
She told me you were gonna break up
with me.
You know that's not true.
I don't know that's not true,
because you lied, Tyler!
You looked me in the eyes,
and you said "No more secrets."
Please just...
Don't ever talk to me again.
You're gonna wish
you texted me back last night.
I need to see Tyler Hansen.
Tyler Hansen, come with me.
And bring your things.
What's going on?
I'm gonna have to ask you
to clear out your locker
and leave the school immediately.
What, am I in trouble?
Tyler, you're being suspended
indefinitely.
One of our students has accused you
of assault.
A police report has been filed.
Elizabeth Viola claims you assaulted her.
I can assure you
this is no laughing matter.
- Who?
- Elizabeth Holly Viola.
I know this doesn't sound like you,
but I have to take these things seriously.
Unbelievable.
"Elizabeth...
Viola."
Have fun.
- Okay, be safe. We love you.
- Bye.
Hello.
I know you probably
don't wanna hear from me.
Holly, I'm not sure I can do this.
I don't even know where to start.
I know,
it kills me that he let this happen.
Are you okay, babe?
No, no, not really.
I know how much it hurts
when you lose something so special.
Yeah.
I want you to know...
I'm here for you.
Gil, listen,
I know you think I'm paranoid,
but I need your help, okay?
I'm headed to 323 Waverly right now.
I think Holly did something to Alison,
so just call me after you get this, okay?
Holly, what are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
Well, I'm using you.
I mean, that is what you people do, right?
- Use each other to get what you want.
- He tried to tell me.
Yeah, he did,
so why didn't you just listen to him?
I mean, you believed everything I said.
Even the baby.
- What does that say about you?
- I thought we were friends.
Listen, Holly, if you let me go,
I won't tell anyone.
Okay, we could just forget
it ever happened. It's not too late.
It was too late the moment I met him.
He had my heart, and I had his.
Then ask him... if that's what love is.
It's not manipulation.
Even if it means you have to let him go.
You need to let him go.
I don't need to ask him who he loves, Ali,
because I know he loves me.
No, he doesn't.
Oh. Looks like your little boyfriend
arrived earlier than expected.
Tyler.
Looks like you're gonna have to see
something you don't wanna see.
No.
No. Please, don't do this.
Elizabeth?
Are you okay?
Elizabeth, what's going on?
Oh, my God.
Behind you.
You found me.
- Sit.
- Holly, what are you doing?
You're gonna have to sit.
Where is Alison?
No.
Now you say, "Where am I?"
Where am I, Holly?
See, that wasn't so difficult.
It's pretty crazy, right?
I've been house-sitting all summer,
and sometimes,
I still can't find my way around.
I can't believe anybody
actually lives here.
Me either.
You see, I've been playing this weekend
over and over in my head,
and now we get to relive it again.
What did you do to her?
I think it's better, just the two of us.
Just like that weekend away.
You, me, in bed together.
Nobody else mattered in the whole world.
You can't look at these photos
and tell me that they mean nothing to you.
- Wow, I love it when you play hard to get.
- Where is Alison?
Alison!
Ali!
Ali?
Holly, I'm listening to you, okay?
But I need you to tell me what you want.
I want us to be together. You, me.
As long as we're together, I don't care.
- So, what do you think?
- Where is she?
Where's Alison? Holly, where is she?
Ali.
Ali, baby. Please, you gotta wake up.
Ali, hey. Hey, it's me. Ali, please.
Ali, please, wake up. Ali, come on.
Oh, thank God.
Ali, it's me.
I'm sorry, baby. Come on.
- Hold on one second.
- Okay.
It's all right.
Come on, let's go.
She killed her.
Tyler.
I got something for you.
There's a door in her bedroom.
Come on.
It's okay.
We're gonna go,
we're gonna get out of here.
- Come on, just a bit further.
- Yoo-hoo.
Sweetness,
why don't you drop that for me?
Drop it.
Okay.
Now what?
Holly, please just listen to me, okay?
I'm sorry.
For everything.
That night that we shared together
was amazing,
and that's something
that nobody can take away from us.
We were just...
We work, you and me together.
- You're right.
- We're perfect together.
Now put down the gun, Holly.
Please.
Put down...
Liar.
Please, don't do anything
you're gonna regret.
Now see, I was even gonna let you live.
Crazy, right?
'Cause it was just so obvious
that Tyler loves me
more than he loves you.
But then,
you just kept getting in the way.
This is my fault, Holly.
Don't take it out on Ali.
I pushed you to this.
This is because of me.
I can't keep lying, all right?
You want me to love you,
but I love Alison, and that's the truth.
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe.
Which one of you is gonna go?
- Wait, Holly.
- Holly!
Ali, get down!
It's crazy how one person
can change your life.
Come on. Let's get out of here.
That's the thing about love.
At first, everything about it seems
to make sense.
But the deeper you get,
the more you realize
you don't know anything at all.
Love teaches you.
Love changes you.
Love makes you do things
you never thought you could do.
It can bring out the best in us.
Or the worst.
Love can destroy you.
I was lucky to survive this...
to make it back to reality.
Some people never escape.
They just can't let go
of their fantasies.
Holly? Holly, can you hear me?
Look, you're going to be okay.
All right?
Don't leave me.
No, I'm not going anywhere.
I got you.
Promise?
But I learned my lesson.
I realized I'd been looking for a fantasy.
Oh, yeah! There it is, Tiff.
Come on.
- But all along...
- Model, girl.
The truth was right in front of me.
Snap. No place I'd rather be.
♪ There is no lesson in magic ♪
♪ There were untimely dreams
Where I knew ♪
♪ Woken in a fog, don't sweat it ♪
♪ And reckon none of it had come
From you ♪
♪ There is no lesson in magic ♪
♪There were untimely dreams
Where I knew ♪
♪ Woken in a fog, don't sweat it ♪
♪ And reckon none of it had come
From you ♪
♪ Pity's sake what we might lose ♪
♪ But in a week might our weakness elude ♪
♪ There was a stagger
That shifted my hips ♪
♪ Oh, how swiftly it shook the dew
From my lips ♪
♪ There was a danger that seeped
From my skull ♪
♪ How it dripped on us all
But it wasn't your fault ♪
♪ We are stranger than Earth
With the seasons misled ♪
♪ Stronger than the moons ♪
♪ When our parts parted
She bled and bled and bled ♪
♪ I wasn't thinkin' about you ♪
♪ Again, again, again, I wasn't thinkin'
About you, I wasn't, I wasn't ♪
♪ Again, again, again
I wasn't thinkin' about you ♪
♪ I wasn't thinkin' about you
♪ Again, again, again
I wasn't thinkin' about you ♪
♪ I wasn't thinkin' about you
I wasn't ♪
♪ And we break downstairs
With our fevers in the air ♪
♪ I forgot to ask
How I only left them there ♪
♪ How thick it sits
And why our eyes glare ♪
♪ Pity's sake what we might lose ♪
♪ But in a week
Might our weakness elude ♪